Call to work at the record.
It's going to be in my city council, my day December 4th, 2023.
Number two, proclamation, recognizing Bill Osborne,
Kobe Island and Osborne drugs for their generosity
in creating the new Christmas ball decorations for the holiday season.
I hope everybody is at the parade, I'm sorry.
There's a great parade, probably one of the best we've had in the long time.
There's been a lot of people there, a lot of entries, but the ball decoration stole the show.
You know, those have been hung in my eye, but from the best of my knowledge and Kobe can correct me
because I know he's a, he's studied these things, but since the 40s, 1927, oh wow,
was the first time those balls were hung and not the ones currently, of course, but
and they were created and built by the city employee.
Alright, Mr. Leonard, is that right? So city employee, Mr. Leonard made the original ones.
I think they were updated maybe in the 40s, maybe.
But they hung till 2007, approximately, and then were damaged in a flood.
So for the last 16 years, we've been without the ball decorations and they've been a talk
every Christmas season, those that talk circulates about, man, we'd love to have those back.
So two to three years ago, Kobe's a thought, right? We kind of got to talk in about how Kobe would be to have those back.
And of course, that started Kobe's engine and he took that on his shoulders and he ran with it.
To try to find a way to bring these things back. He found a partner of Bill Osborne and I was born family.
To help financially get this done. And I know Kobe's made it a mission and he found a group I believe in New Mexico
that made him old and built these out of fiberglass to the, as close to the original specifications that Kobe could find by looking at pictures and pictures and pictures.
And they clam shell, if I remember right where he can open up and work on the inside, but his group drilled up major and drilled all the holes and
we're trying to be as precise as possible to put as many bulbs on there and, but they got it done and power and his group worked get him hung and there's only certain poles that we can hang him on right now.
That's why they're in the areas they are. I know some people are freaking out about the green ones, but that's where we had to hang it.
They had to be hung there and it'll be different when we get done. But at the parade Saturday,
actually before that we did it was being talked about and pictures start circulating.
of the decorations and I had a gentleman named Don Children's Rejoctomy and he lives in Los Angeles
and he was excited that the balls were being recreated and that they were going to be hung,
that he remembered him as a kid.
I mean, you know, I live in a grown-up mile, I remember seeing those and those are always special.
The whales have those.
And I hope nobody else ever has them besides us.
But he remembered those growing up.
And so he had a conversation with me online about how great it was to have him back.
So we was at the Pride Saturday night and I'm on the stage with representatives of Bachelors.
He was presented a check to donate towards the decorations.
And come off the stage.
The gentleman came up, said, are you Mayor Parker?
I am.
He said, I am Don Children's and I message you that today from Los Angeles.
And I flew in for this parade so I can see these balls being hung.
So he was special enough to him that he flew in.
I also know there was another couple that came in from Minnesota to be here because the balls were back.
So I know we talked about how special they are to us.
But they're special to a lot of people.
There's a lot of people we had no idea.
I know that night I was so excited to talk to the Don.
He flew in from California.
He flew in both of them and told them what what I needed and what it means to people.
So I think a lot of times we take for granted what we have in our little town here in Miami.
But man we have some cool stuff.
And just being recreated just it's special.
No balance has it.
And I know after the conversation I had that these two have already talked about maybe adding some more.
So these later so this make it more special.
So they're building more of these traditions for our grandkids and our great grandkids.
So means a lot to me because we enjoyed it for generations and generations.
And now more kids will be able to enjoy it for more generations.
So if the council approves without proclamations that we can hand out to these guys.
Thank you man.
And Sean our gratitude for what they did to bring these back.
Second.
There we go.
Parker.
Hi.
He's dead.
If he goes comfortable.
Hi.
I'll have one, three, public input or on-skidled personal praises.
We have one, Mr. Beck-Jim. Thank you, guys.
I just wanted to remind you and remind the community that there'll be a public meeting on Thursday evening at 530.
Here at the Civic Center to talk about the finding city PA has finally done for us for this swimming hole along the one-third of a mile area.
Along Tark Creek and it's important information and how happy we are about what good can happen here.
This is the thing we need to know about so we can really fight to have a better and cleaner creek so children can play safely and swim safely in that area.
The meeting will be run by a contractor that EPA has hired.
Our name is Carmen King. She's very reputable. She will interpret the data from the study that EPA did.
They did it along that creek and where we have been monitoring basically two swimming holes.
They found five and along the stream that they found more than we had been monitoring.
There's a lot of use of the creek and we wanted to be used in the future and we should be now.
I think the information is going to be important for the community to have and I think important for the city to understand very seriously.
To push EPA to make this better.
So I appreciate you and we've got some handouts over.
leave them up here at the door. This is what we're handing out in the neighborhood. It just tells
that people can attend the meeting in person. Are they can do it by teams on the
evening? So I'll leave these for you and I encourage you to attend.
Thank you.
Four claims.
Okay.
Five minutes from the number.
20th.
Five?
Five.
Six presentation from the MIMA area at the access services.
A few very much,
and speak to you, but things that are happening at the MyMaria Economic Development Service.
I do want to note that I did have a wonderful, beautiful presentation for each and
I, with somebody in the opportunity.
Let me give it a little bit of a hard time.
It could be a real short and sweet and probably the shortest presentation you've ever had for me.
Just some real quick updates.
We just had a board meeting last week.
So we reelected officers or elected officers for the 2024 year.
Our president, our chairperson, excuse me, will remain Heather Lillard.
Brett Hayes, with total on us, will remain as the Vice Chairperson.
And our new Secretary Treasurer's Cameron Wilkins from Security Bank and Trust.
We also re-appointed four board members whose terms were expiring.
So those board members who were continuing with us are Nick High Smith, Nick Bowers,
Kirk Williams and Chairperson Lillard.
The other thing I want to quickly bring your attention to is, and this is something you're going to be hearing from us.
Over the next few weeks, we are beginning work on a new economic development strategic plan.
Through the MyMaria Economic Development Service, we have contracted with Jim Fram, with community strategies.
Jim is very knowledgeable.
His experience in economic development is second to nine.
He is going to be leading that effort.
We are going to be reaching out to each one of you on the council for your input.
People will be scheduling meetings and focus groups to gather some information from you.
So help us as we pull this plan together.
There's going to be meetings that will start taking place in January.
There will be some community meetings as well.
So we're very excited about this.
It's a great opportunity to help shape the direction, not only of the MyMaria Economic Development Service.
but our economic developments throughout this part of Oklahoma.
We're reaching out to other communities like Comber,
Square Land, Quapal, wine.app.
And the need to grow our primary focus is always what happens here in Miami,
and Ottawa County, but there's also some tie-ins,
obviously with what is taking place throughout the region.
So I hope you will participate.
Attend those meetings.
You're going to enjoy working with Jim Fram.
If you don't know him, once you get to know him,
you're going to really appreciate his sense of humor.
And more importantly, his dedication to growing to economic development,
especially strategic planning.
The other things that we've been working on today,
I spent some time working with Jeremy, with model.
They were, he was running into some issues,
with needing to find some forms to complete.
For their state incentives,
they will track that information down, get those to them.
Jeremy is bringing his family down this weekend.
They're driving down Friday.
They will be here next week.
So we're excited to meet with him again,
and to finalize some of those applications for economic incentives.
In cinnives, they have made an offer on property within the industrial park.
That offer was accepted,
and they have until December 22nd to close on that property.
So those are really, that's all I have.
Just wanted to get up here and just kind of keep you at the day on
some of the things we're doing and working on.
Happy to answer any questions for you at this time.
How's the spec building project going?
I think building project is moving forward.
Last I talked to Chris Butler with BPC.
They were hoping to start interviewing before the end of the year.
They're start data set that officially yet,
but they were going to start.
I think trying to interview people,
I start filling some of those positions by the end of the year.
These are great jobs if you remember.
The lowest paid starting position there is like 47-5 a year.
Great opportunity for families to give quality job and good benefits.
So you said that would be right after the first of the year.
You think it would be up and going?
I'm going to, I had the ballpark, and I'm going to say February.
Okay.
There's still some issues that they're dealing with,
but I think they're moving out with basically pretty quickly.
So these guys are aggressive.
A lot like multiple days coming from Oregon,
the folks on the west coast don't waste a lot of time.
When they get here, they're making after it.
Any other leads on any other stuff?
Working on a few days.
That's that.
There you go.
Any other questions for Hannah?
Did he get an answer?
That I can answer our question.
But it's not that we try to be secretive.
Because we don't want to do that.
Because you guys are obviously a tremendous partner to us and everything that we do.
Within the major organization.
But we do have to be careful when on things that we discuss.
Competitiality is a very, very important just.
But I have had several conversations today included.
So we've got options.
We've been working on some things.
And as in trust me as we can.
You will know.
I promise you.
Thank you, Shannon.
Yes, sir.
Thanks, sir.
Thank you.
Seven.
Revoke.
Policy.
You see you.
20.
15.
Desire.
One.
Develop.
Revives.
A repeal policy.
So I'm going to backtrack this a little bit to your last meeting.
I did the research on that.
I looked.
I actually.
We have a group email appears with city clerks and treasures that we.
Do you know, so I emailed them to see what they did for their policies.
I.
I looked at 10 different softwares.
I narrowed down to three.
I brought it.
And we did actual demos of that software.
Then we took it to.
We had a meeting kind of a committee.
And we made it back to the building boat both on that and.
The contract was just by far most economical the price that I found on those 10.
I went anywhere from 4,400 to 26,500.
So this was a very economical one.
And we just learned it for policies.
When we did the demo, we seeing that it could probably do other things.
Track other documents.
So I just kind of wanted to answer that.
And I do well, so some good things again about.
about Doctrack is. It tells the person who uploads their document exactly where it's at in the
approval process. It can track hopefully, well, I know it will track more things than just
policies and procedures. There is, you can set up a lot of MAC reminders to review it a year
or two later. Employees can attest that they have read it. The departments can create a quiz to
make sure they comprehend what they've read. And then there's a public access portal that we
will have a link on our website to go to, so you can see those policies for sure and some
probably SOPs for some departments. So now I'm going to go to this. I'm requesting that you
revoke the current policy because during all this conversation, we really legal came to the conclusion
that policy, we don't need to be thrown around that, we're will, we need to reserve that term
for statutory required policies, and of which there are approximately 21 give or take in state statutes.
So everything else we either be called SOP, standard operating procedure or an SOE sequence of events.
And SOP, I'm going to give you example, it kind of tells you the what and why.
So something that we have is a cache handling policy.
So if you accept cache on behalf of the city of Miami,
we tell you exactly how to do it and where it goes and what's the timing and all that,
that would be an SOP.
And SOE is really more detailed instructions that's inside of a department.
So something that I've sent out many times is, how do you run a revenue expense report?
That's short, sweet instruction.
So that's something that you can do.
So I'm going to show you the difference.
Our current policy, which we definitely don't want to call the policy,
because it's not statutory required, but right here, it's not about right now.
We call everything about this either, or another body policy.
Again, we want to change that, because it does help reduce our risk,
because you don't want to call everything policy.
No, don't jump in if you want to.
So there are any questions that I would like to.
Okay, so how across this first right now is the policy is emailed to me.
There is a review committee, I sent it out to them, they have seven days.
If it affects the union, they have 10 days, so it's seven days for them to review.
It moves on regardless.
At this point, a policy is then sent to legal.
Now, policies right now in this policy, procedures live inside policies.
That's something over here.
This is new SOP that I created, this is a draft form, it is in your packet.
It's not finalized yet, it's pretty close.
All of these procedures will be separated.
Right now, procedures can change at all the time.
Because you get different people, you get different titles, you get different duties,
and that happens all the time.
Policies do not, because they're law, and they change more less frequently.
So this is going to be what the time savings is.
So if it's an SOP, there are only 10 days due to the legal assistant to review that SOP.
And if she has any questions, she'll take them to bin, and they'll either red flag it or it'll just move on.
So that means within 20 days, will we have the acknowledging the approval process?
Which it could be way different than everything, even poll procedures going to legal.
That really glets the system when that happens.
Because there's always more things.
It's important to policy until we need it.
So that's kind of different.
So the part and red is the difference.
And why it's so important that we revoke this policy, because it's not statutory or required.
And this SOP will help us move things through faster.
So you're saying that all of our policies will be backed up by a state statute?
Yes.
Which it should be anywhere.
Correct.
So they're mandated by a state statute.
But I mean, so they have a particular significance, legal significance, and are people in that
important.
Did you follow the policy?
You should not do this something.
I may follow.
Mr. Beckett, by the way, statute.
Right.
So what I'm asking for is to revoke the policy COU-21501.
So, I don't know if anyone else watches YouTube, first amendment auditors or not, but I've
watched a few.
And that's what they always ask, because people say it's a policy, and then first question
to ask, what statute makes up that policy.
And a lot of times, there's not one, because in this case, they call a policy, they call
a lot of things policy, but they're not, they're not, they're not, they're not statute.
They're not statute.
They're not.
I think, in the most cases, it's just a policy that's supposed to be followed by employees, not by
somebody in front of them.
All make a motion that we approve this.
We revoked this.
We revoked this, but we approve this.
We have to approve the revocation.
Yes.
OK.
There you go.
Second.
All right.
Thank you, Jill.
Thanks, Jill.
I'm going to kill you, Ryan.
So, Brian, eight through 11 of the same ones we want to do.
MSUA.
Eight.
Award annual on call of concrete.
Repair C23, 58 columns.
The structure kept me.
Hascofabrication construction.
There was concrete construction.
Stocks construction.
And these construction.
But this year, 2324.
Can I make a motion?
We approve items eight through.
Well, we can't.
I mean, we can't vote on this.
Why?
But you do that was not to vote.
Yes.
So, we make motion.
Eight.
Now, do we do not to vote.
I'll make a motion.
I approve it.
I'm having eight.
Second.
Perfect.
December.
Stain.
I.
Defcore.
High.
All right.
And then.
I make a motion.
Approved line out of nine through 12.
11.
Not to vote.
I'm going to vote.
And you yell at me.
Second.
I'm going to vote.
Parker.
December.
Hi.
William.
Defcore.
Hi.
East.
12 discussion.
Impossible action on opt.
Opt.
The proposed 3M.
PFA S class action lawsuit and on ratifying dropped out of the proposed DuPont PFA S
five section lawsuit sent on November 30th, 2023 by the city manager.
So, a couple of weeks ago we hired the method tab off to represent us on the five section
lawsuits that are pending by the Bay of Demous Research, not only for us, but some of the
other responsibilities that they're representing, both of these lawsuits, the means, or not
to participate in the settlements and the one they thought, a 3M lawsuit is the larger
of the two.
It's a $12 billion, a smaller one, lawsuit, and so the one they estimated that if we stayed
in those lawsuits, at least in the every year of what that is to compensate us for, was going
to be a $2,000 from now on through the turning to those things, you're not going to
not get the money that the things come out.
The most important thing though is on the lawsuit they had to have with the mayor and the vice mayor
of those conversations, but with the head and sent him, essentially, because that's the deadline for
the pre-M lawsuit is tomorrow, so based on what you do today, to an important situation,
and really, I don't feel like it's probably explained to us the time frame that they were giving
us, because they didn't tell us.
a few days before that, that we needed to decide if we were going to opt out, but they never explained
the deadline until they called us and said, how come you haven't done something?
You haven't told us we had to do something.
So it's unfortunate.
I apologize to you all that we didn't have this information before.
But that's fair.
Unfortunately, we're still in a type window time frame for the bigger lawsuit at this point.
The catch there are the email that they sent, explaining why they thought we should opt out, as well as the mode sent to them last.
How many municipalities you think are in this?
Well, it's every municipality I'm speculating at this, but it should be every municipality in the country.
So it's not just municipalities that have a water system problem.
It would also include rural water districts, co-bunch, maybe counties, yeah, it's going to be a bunch.
And this could go on for however, the obligation to test for the municipalities to pass the other thing and list all the,
say I'm not that familiar with the terminology that we have.
The ambassadors and others, and others, and others, and others.
The obligation could exist forever.
We've been notified, we've been notified that we have to start testing for this.
We don't know what the cost is going to be, but it's going to be very extensive.
148,000 public water systems in the United States.
How much?
148,000.
That's a possibility.
148.
So that's a possibility.
People could be in this.
Also municipalities that have airports will have a larger share of more, more appropriately, larger airports.
We haven't sprayed on the swimming.
It's not sprayed a whole lot of this, but this is where they have sprayed a lot of it.
Well, based on what he just gave us, we're looking at that, you want $1,000.
That's if it's evenly divided.
We're all right.
Bigger, the entity, the more they're going to be given.
Right, sure.
We probably get like $8,000.
But you're recognizing me.
We just cut our losses.
My recommendation is we follow what the experts,
that know a whole lot more about this or tell us.
Well, we got together and talk.
That's kind of the conversations that we have because
we know how many lawsuits we've been involved in already,
and we're lawsuit sick around here.
We don't need to spend any more of our citizens running against
paying lawyers.
Well, I opinion.
The thing is, we voted to hire these guys,
or sign all of these guys, these guys are just,
and we ought to out.
Yeah.
So, when lawyers tell me that they don't want your money,
then you should listen.
We don't have to.
It's why that would be.
Well, okay.
So, we're talking now.
We just preserve our rights for just,
could mean later on.
There would be other litigation.
But for right now, this is,
these are the two lawsuits that are proceeding
that we know of.
And they have a swist in.
It is a claimant in both of them.
Unless we opt out.
We don't really need to opt out of the other one.
No right.
I mean, should we need to.
We need to.
We need to get that.
We have to get that.
They should find that.
They already opt out of one.
If you all approve, we'll opt out of the other one.
But that does reserve a right for future litigation.
We decide it's worth it.
It's a point of the future.
But you, as a moral.
Which probably, I mean, most likely,
what's going to happen is there's going to be more litigation.
Class action lawsuits in the future,
that they think will bring us more money.
That better fit us.
We'll make a motion that we opt out.
Take a vote for them.
Okay.
All right.
William.
Thank you.
All right.
13.
To my commission agreement,
for AdZell,
at the MCFA Stadium.
So the MCFA is the stadium trust authority.
They have contracts with each of the three entities.
They've comprised the MCFA.
That's the college and the public schools in the city of Mayan.
I've already have contracts with the other two that if they sell any ads.
I'll be back in there.
on the scoreboard or on the signing facility
that they get a commission for selling that.
The city of Miami to the best.
My knowledge has never sold and had there, but we could.
We could.
That commission.
It just keeps us on a car with.
You mean it's very likely, Chaps?
It is absolutely likely that we could.
Sure.
It's going to be a group.
It's like.
Okay.
Let's go.
14.
Now the new business.
The business of posting this.
The agenda.
15.
Staff reports.
16.
Maricados.
Community announcements.
We talked about the.
Awesome.
I had several people mention that.
They felt like people were too crowded in this year.
Like.
Set one.
Chairs up right next to the where the things were.
I mean, especially down here.
So I don't know how we fixed that.
What was the same last year?
Was it?
Yeah.
The last year we were further down.
So I didn't see this bad.
But it seemed like there's more people there this year.
But it didn't seem like there anymore.
So I don't know what we.
What we can do to keep people.
I mean back back in the day, we had to stay on the side.
But I mean if there's more people.
There's more people.
So we have to.
We have to allow that.
But then I think there's going to be a way to.
Some of the times when when they were throwing candy out, the kids were running right up to.
The cars and.
I mean, not hate for a kid to get ran over by a folder truck or something.
And it seemed like the more they threw candy the more they would squeeze in.
And just to me presented a situation.
I heard others make comments about it too.
Yeah.
Sometimes I think about.
I wouldn't thought it'd been that big of a deal right after Halloween.
And then those two blocks of chapters and.
And maybe four central.
They get's real bottleneck.
Yeah.
Real tight.
It was tight.
I mean, I would have to parade men.
Todd.
And it was.
It was.
The kids were getting in front of the little kids and.
We're.
I didn't know it.
I tried to.
They're good of it.
Some.
That situations in.
I don't know what the answer is, but I think we should get some ideas.
All the way.
But overall it's great of it. Well, but I feel like I guess probably the biggest one we've had
There's a lot of people
Seeing that very many people like that a long time has anybody seen anything drone footage
I thought it was just had that his drone out no high tower didn't
Yeah, he's up to him, but there was a
I don't know who had their drone out. There was a one but I don't know who's a one
It's one of one of the somebody's got drone footage. It'd be great to see all of our businesses were slammed that night too
And I wanted I wanted to be right after horse to get eats for the family. I'm and they were just packed
Scooters was packed
Every business you went by down Main Street just was packed
It was amazing
I had to park
North of Barbies, I parked in the ditch because I had my clothes on
Good problem to have
I want to say
Thank you to all of our city staff
Because that was the one heck of a parade and we couldn't have done it without you and your efforts
I think you guys get overlooked sometimes for the effort you guys put in Tyler Kevin
You got your crews make her downtown look great for Christmas and other things so and it goes all the way back to everybody
It's not just those crews. It's a team effort
So I appreciate you guys
Because we had a great parade because if you guys and our chamber did a great job mainstream did a good job
Just team effort. I like the direction we're going. I like the moment and we have
Our businesses as they said we're all packed and they I know they all loved it
We talked to several of them today
But when I had lunch a good fellas and
Bobby it good fellas couldn't say enough good things about how things were going for him down town
You know the ice cream guy was we were in there while go and he
Was great scooters have their
largest opening in the region
Saturday he said it was better even than the scooters at the hard rock in Katusa
They made more that day they call me back Sunday and said Sunday was better than Saturday
And then when I went through there the afternoon he said they were on pace today to beat Saturday and Sunday
So then I called Eli at the frozen elephant and he said he had a great weekend in both places and he was didn't really well
Better than normal so
You know just get people down to those events getting people out
Just working and off our businesses, but
I just want to say thank you to you guys all you guys at the city
We couldn't do without you
I really appreciate the momentum we're getting down to you with doing these events and it's something that we didn't do before but I think I think the moral
We do down there the bigger it's going to be all right so you know we started back in November with the
kick off the Christmas kick off, right? And that was Dallas huge and we talked about that and then this I just think it all kind of snowballing and creating a
Just a buzz where everybody's going to be more involved in the spooky world than having all the businesses
Participate in the window painting. Oh, yeah, a little pain is great. Yeah, and again
What they have three winners?
Five action.
They had an honorable mention and had to get into a total of choices.
And then that's what they did.
Yeah.
I hope so.
There are so three traveling trophies.
One went to the Facebook, everybody went on Facebook.
So people's choice.
So I got to go on Facebook and vote for the one they wanted.
Then there were small window, which Aussies won that.
The people's choice was pros and elephant.
And then best overall was color organization.
And I can't see their windows.
I thought they were posters.
I think they look on.
Jessica Stout did those.
Unbelievable.
Wow.
They looked really good.
So if you get a chance to go buy and take a look.
But again, thank all of you guys because the thing I see is we're moving as a unit.
We're all going the same direction.
Everybody's working hard for the same thing.
And people are seeing it.
And there are people not just from here or saying that people from other places are seeing it.
That we get calls.
We had two national chains here last week.
Looking for property.
But restaurants in.
We're being noticed.
So he's up to good work.
We appreciate you.
We're going to read my on the moving forward together.
Yes.
That's all I got.
They've asked for what we've gone.
So did those trophies go to the businesses?
Yep.
They get them from the whole year.
You're going to present outfit and then have one.
I guess.
I mean, it'll be there for a year.
Then those cool.
But there's a nine point to be on it.
And then the next year they'll break back and keep you on another plate night for the next one.
They'll get cheaper for the year.
So she's the one that's doing the photos with them.
I don't know.
I know she will be there.
She told me I could go if I wanted to go.
But if you guys want to go, we can all go.
Well.
I don't know if we can all go.
Two of us.
But two of us.
Let's go.
And you know.
There was some that Kishu was having a problem getting some people going.
So I started to send them text messages saying, hey, we need you.
And so I know five alarm was one of them that she tried to get.
They said, I don't know.
I do it.
So I put some pressure on them.
They called in to get in.
She said, I thought you guys were going to do it.
They said, I don't know.
I don't know.
So we're going to do it.
But David Davis, I made him do it.
I put pressure on him.
But it was good.
It means really cool to go down down to see all of it.
It's awesome right now.
So it really does.
And there's some pretty talented people.
sure how that's going yet. If you guys, if you don't, I should. So, so, let's start.
Can you get the check today?
Yeah.
Hey, what do we have with the fire truck?
I don't know.
Can you give us a stop date on it?
Next Christmas?
It'll set out.
So, what do we do? Is there anything we can do?
The fire, set it back a little bit.
Oh, got you.
Was it in there?
No.
Okay.
So, how far away are we from having that?
I mean, the next Christmas was out of goal.
We can, to you.
Hey, we can always set a goal.
We can always set a goal.
Yeah.
Let's do it for each Christmas.
20, 30.
Good luck.
Next year?
We have 12 months.
Good.
But that's just 20, 24.
So, we need to get in charge of that truck.
Go ahead.
How many guys are required?
I'm going to blow it up and...
Water is pushing it.
I'll say your first, but we can't.
Okay.
So, you have here, right here.
If the next meeting...
We'll talk about it.
You can talk about it.
He's all fired up, and you guys can do it.
All right.
Anything else?
Boom.
All right.
So we'll go on the 17, sigmanders communications.
I want to thank Melinda for jumping in there and helping leave that team.
For jumping in there and helping lead that team for the tree lighting.
Absolutely.
I forgot about that school.
Just an amazing event.
Tyler, you and your team.
Kevin, you and Zem.
Chuck and Rodney and everybody came together to make that whole night really special.
It's not the big chamber event like the parade is, but wow, we've turned it into something.
Great turnout.
Great time.
The tree looked wonderful.
But in the work we'll be hit it.
I was really important.
The kids all loved it.
They were all excited.
The glow sticks eventually started working the next night.
in my car in the next night.
Anyway, you know, it started off as just, I think, year or so ago, we just had the tree lighting,
and then we had the choir of the junior high come seeing, and then we decided,
we really liked that we should cut here, so we put it on stage, we gave it a microphone,
they did an amazing job, we had the dancers there,
not cracker I think it was, came in there deal, the whole thing was just incredible.
So we talked about, but we're thinking that we just need more space,
so next year we'll probably spread out a little bit.
He let's not want to say, he was talking about a taller tree, right?
No, we already have the tallest tree on Route 66, I found out.
We're just going to put lights on the oak tree to co-use.
Put the right away, guys, we're going to shake it a little bit.
That's in greenery today.
It's greenery.
Nobody had a little bit of it.
No, it was a great event, thank you for what you did.
In Kevin Beauty, your team was fantastic.
It just kind of all comes together.
I appreciate everybody's effort on that.
The arrangement and the rest of it was awesome.
So it's a long-fersement agent from Carl Dungeon, and she told me she had a blast.
Yeah, she was a great sport.
She's a great sport.
She's great.
She's a she ended up on the buckshot Monday.
Yeah, I was on there today.
It was awesome.
It was a great event.
It was great.
So thanks to everybody.
It really does mean a lot.
Can't wait for next year to see what happens.
And I want to say two.
I forgot to say this on my time.
But Derek Scythney, who is the filmmaker for Congressman Rakeen.
And by the end of the parade he was there.
And he said it was the best parade.
He's ever been to.
Yeah, it's all family down.
Yeah.
He's on that right truck.
Now he was even just a spectator.
Yeah.
He just brought a family up to watch his girls and they used to have an amazing time.
But he's became a good, good, good community partner with us.
Yeah.
And so we invited him to come.
He brought his family.
He says one of the best parade he's ever been to.
And I got a lot of really good feedback from people about the parade as well.
Yeah.
Good weekend.
I think we have.
I'm sorry.
I'm tracking your time here up here.
Yeah.
I think Kisha has an event coming up on December 18th called Shopping and Sipping.
Sipping shop.
Something like that.
And it's a event for.
It's a shop downtown.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's on.
We have a council meeting that night on the 18th.
But it's for ladies to shop downtown.
And you'll be able to do a wish list.
And at the end of the night, your wish list will be text to your spouse.
Your boyfriend, whatever.
maybe, though, you're wishless to me.
See you.
That way.
Huh?
Poor folks.
You're the first.
There you go.
That way.
Well, all minutes your husband doesn't know what to get you, and there's five
to be one.
Where your dad is.
It's a neat idea.
But Tisha's really good.
I need to bring him to his place.
He's a little pressure on you, you know, so you can get that.
But Tisha's got a lot of energy now down, the businesses are really responding to her
well.
And if you get out of the industry, you're probably going to see her walking up and down
it, going in and out of a business, I think, I think about every day I see her going somewhere
down there.
But she's going to give you a job.
That makes me a program that's phenomenal.
She has just to steal her job, get this thing off the ground.
Can they else?
Nope.
18 in Germany.
Okay.